## **CONOR PARRISH**

Developer, Entrepreneur, Technical Leader

# conorparrish.com

720-209-5425 conor.parrish@icloud.com Boulder, CO

### Summary

I am a developer with skills and experience across the stack, from DevOps all the way up to front end design. Through starting my own company, I gained enthusiasm for working with customers to understand their needs and set requirements. I thrive most in collaboration with others, and I work to make an immediate, positive impact.

#### Education

University of Colorado Boulder - B.S. Computer Science, 3.6 GPA, May 2018

### Experience

Co-Founder, Hearth; Boulder, CO - 2017 - present

Bootstrapped the development of a smart home hardware product from the ground up through rigorous customer development, project management, and coding work.

Software Engineering Intern, Visa Inc.; Denver, CO — Summer 2017
As a member of Visa's Network Processing team, I revamped critical internal data visualization tools and deployed my solutions to the company's worldwide network.

Director, HackCU; Boulder, CO - 2016 - 2018

As Director of HackCU, Colorado's largest collegiate hackathon, I slashed costs and scaled the event from 150 to 600 participants with a focus on inclusivity.

Lead Web Designer, ASSETT, CU Boulder; Boulder, CO -2015 - 2016 I trained new employees and led the technical process of redesigning and migrating dozens of university department websites onto a brand-new platform.

#### Coding

Python, C++, JavaScript, Java, HTML, CSS, MySQL

By fully understanding the fundamental principles of programming languages, I adapt efficiently to new software stacks and environments, resulting in diverse, flexible abilities in programming and web development.

#### **Skills**

In addition to my coding skills, I excel in customer development, graphic design, and conversational Spanish. I have the ability to self-teach and procure important information with minimal supervision.

#### **Personal Interests**

I am passionate about the outdoors, especially skiing and mountaineering. I play the guitar and enjoy traveling to new places, most recently France.